Hi, I’m Blaine Beshah, the Global Merchant for Gap Fit, and I’m here
to talk to you guys about January.
This is a huge month for Fit, where our customer is making New Year’s
resolutions and she definitely needs a new workout wardrobe
to help her get back in shape.
To help support our customer in her New Year’s resolutions,
we have some great performance pieces in our January line.
We’re most excited about our marble prints, which are offered in tops,
bottoms, and sports bras, to inject a little bit of fashion into her outfit.
We’re also really excited about our Studio pieces, which are great
for wearing to and from the gym.
We have foam-bonded sweatshirts and bombers, that look really great
paired over everything else that we offer in our Jan assortment.
Again, January is a very important month for Fit, with our customer
really looking to us to help her meet her New Year’s resolutions.
By pushing the marble printed styles, as well as our Studio foam-bonded
pieces, you’ll help us drive great value and win the month of January.
Thank you.